[
  {
    "Question": "鎂",
    "Answer1": "Li",
    "Answer2": "K",
    "Answer3": "Ca",
    "correct": "Mg"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鋰",
    "Answer1": "Na",
    "Answer2": "Hg",
    "Answer3": "Ti",
    "correct": "Li"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鈉",
    "Answer1": "Al",
    "Answer2": "Ca",
    "Answer3": "Cu",
    "correct": "Na"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鋁",
    "Answer1": "K",
    "Answer2": "Ti",
    "Answer3": "Fe",
    "correct": "Al"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鉀",
    "Answer1": "Hg",
    "Answer2": "Cu",
    "Answer3": "Au",
    "correct": "K"
  },
  {
    "Question": "汞",
    "Answer1": "Ca",
    "Answer2": "Fe",
    "Answer3": "Pt",
    "correct": "Hg"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鈣",
    "Answer1": "Ti",
    "Answer2": "Au",
    "Answer3": "W",
    "correct": "Ca"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鈦",
    "Answer1": "Cu",
    "Answer2": "Pt",
    "Answer3": "Mn",
    "correct": "Ti"
  },
  {
    "Question": "銅",
    "Answer1": "Fe",
    "Answer2": "W",
    "Answer3": "Ag",
    "correct": "Cu"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鐵",
    "Answer1": "Au",
    "Answer2": "Mn",
    "Answer3": "Pb",
    "correct": "Fe"
  },
  {
    "Question": "金",
    "Answer1": "Pt",
    "Answer2": "Ag",
    "Answer3": "C",
    "correct": "Au"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鉑",
    "Answer1": "W",
    "Answer2": "Pb",
    "Answer3": "Si",
    "correct": "Pt"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鎢",
    "Answer1": "Mn",
    "Answer2": "C",
    "Answer3": "S",
    "correct": "W"
  },
  {
    "Question": "錳",
    "Answer1": "Ag",
    "Answer2": "Si",
    "Answer3": "I",
    "correct": "Mn"
  },
  {
    "Question": "銀",
    "Answer1": "Pb",
    "Answer2": "S",
    "Answer3": "P",
    "correct": "Ag"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鉛",
    "Answer1": "C",
    "Answer2": "I",
    "Answer3": "Br",
    "correct": "Pb"
  },
  {
    "Question": "碳",
    "Answer1": "Si",
    "Answer2": "P",
    "Answer3": "H",
    "correct": "C"
  },
  {
    "Question": "矽",
    "Answer1": "S",
    "Answer2": "Br",
    "Answer3": "N",
    "correct": "Si"
  },
  {
    "Question": "硫",
    "Answer1": "I",
    "Answer2": "H",
    "Answer3": "O",
    "correct": "S"
  },
  {
    "Question": "碘",
    "Answer1": "P",
    "Answer2": "N",
    "Answer3": "Cl",
    "correct": "I"
  },
  {
    "Question": "磷",
    "Answer1": "Br",
    "Answer2": "O",
    "Answer3": "Ar",
    "correct": "P"
  },
  {
    "Question": "溴",
    "Answer1": "H",
    "Answer2": "Cl",
    "Answer3": "He",
    "correct": "Br"
  },
  {
    "Question": "氫",
    "Answer1": "N",
    "Answer2": "Ar",
    "Answer3": "Rb",
    "correct": "H"
  },
  {
    "Question": "氮",
    "Answer1": "O",
    "Answer2": "He",
    "Answer3": "Cs",
    "correct": "N"
  },
  {
    "Question": "氧",
    "Answer1": "Cl",
    "Answer2": "Rb",
    "Answer3": "Fr",
    "correct": "O"
  },
  {
    "Question": "氯",
    "Answer1": "Ar",
    "Answer2": "Cs",
    "Answer3": "Be",
    "correct": "Cl"
  },
  {
    "Question": "氬",
    "Answer1": "He",
    "Answer2": "Fr",
    "Answer3": "Sr",
    "correct": "Ar"
  },
  {
    "Question": "氦",
    "Answer1": "Rb",
    "Answer2": "Be",
    "Answer3": "Ba",
    "correct": "He"
  },
  {
    "Question": "銣",
    "Answer1": "Cs",
    "Answer2": "Sr",
    "Answer3": "Ra",
    "correct": "Rb"
  },
  {
    "Question": "銫",
    "Answer1": "Fr",
    "Answer2": "Ba",
    "Answer3": "B",
    "correct": "Cs"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鍅",
    "Answer1": "Be",
    "Answer2": "Ra",
    "Answer3": "Ga",
    "correct": "Fr"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鈹",
    "Answer1": "Sr",
    "Answer2": "B",
    "Answer3": "In",
    "correct": "Be"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鍶",
    "Answer1": "Ba",
    "Answer2": "Ga",
    "Answer3": "Tl",
    "correct": "Sr"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鋇",
    "Answer1": "Ra",
    "Answer2": "In",
    "Answer3": "Ge",
    "correct": "Ba"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鐳",
    "Answer1": "B",
    "Answer2": "Tl",
    "Answer3": "Sn",
    "correct": "Ra"
  },
  {
    "Question": "硼",
    "Answer1": "Ga",
    "Answer2": "Ge",
    "Answer3": "As",
    "correct": "B"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鎵",
    "Answer1": "In",
    "Answer2": "Sn",
    "Answer3": "Sb",
    "correct": "Ga"
  },
  {
    "Question": "銦",
    "Answer1": "Tl",
    "Answer2": "As",
    "Answer3": "Bi",
    "correct": "In"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鉈",
    "Answer1": "Ge",
    "Answer2": "Sb",
    "Answer3": "Se",
    "correct": "Tl"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鍺",
    "Answer1": "Sn",
    "Answer2": "Bi",
    "Answer3": "Te",
    "correct": "Ge"
  },
  {
    "Question": "錫",
    "Answer1": "As",
    "Answer2": "Se",
    "Answer3": "Po",
    "correct": "Sn"
  },
  {
    "Question": "砷",
    "Answer1": "Sb",
    "Answer2": "Te",
    "Answer3": "At",
    "correct": "As"
  },
  {
    "Question": "銻",
    "Answer1": "Bi",
    "Answer2": "Po",
    "Answer3": "Ne",
    "correct": "Sb"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鉍",
    "Answer1": "Se",
    "Answer2": "At",
    "Answer3": "Kr",
    "correct": "Bi"
  },
  {
    "Question": "硒",
    "Answer1": "Te",
    "Answer2": "Ne",
    "Answer3": "Xe",
    "correct": "Se"
  },
  {
    "Question": "碲",
    "Answer1": "Po",
    "Answer2": "Kr",
    "Answer3": "Rn",
    "correct": "Te"
  },
  {
    "Question": "釙",
    "Answer1": "At",
    "Answer2": "Xe",
    "Answer3": "Cd",
    "correct": "Po"
  },
  {
    "Question": "砈",
    "Answer1": "Ne",
    "Answer2": "Rn",
    "Answer3": "Co",
    "correct": "At"
  },
  {
    "Question": "氖",
    "Answer1": "Kr",
    "Answer2": "Cd",
    "Answer3": "Ni",
    "correct": "Ne"
  },
  {
    "Question": "氪",
    "Answer1": "Xe",
    "Answer2": "Co",
    "Answer3": "Mg",
    "correct": "Kr"
  },
  {
    "Question": "氙",
    "Answer1": "Rn",
    "Answer2": "Ni",
    "Answer3": "Li",
    "correct": "Xe"
  },
  {
    "Question": "氡",
    "Answer1": "Cd",
    "Answer2": "Mg",
    "Answer3": "Na",
    "correct": "Rn"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鎘",
    "Answer1": "Co",
    "Answer2": "Li",
    "Answer3": "Al",
    "correct": "Cd"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鈷",
    "Answer1": "Ni",
    "Answer2": "Na",
    "Answer3": "K",
    "correct": "Co"
  },
  {
    "Question": "鎳",
    "Answer1": "Mg",
    "Answer2": "Al",
    "Answer3": "P",
    "correct": "Ni"
  }
]